[MUSIC]
Our aim in this derivatives course was to
show you how to practically invest and
trading these often complex option and
future financial instruments.
You should now know that an equity
option is essentially derived from
the future performance of a stock,
exchange traded fund or similar product.
This is the derivative nature of options.
You should also have the skills to
distinguish between call and put options.
Identify the components of an options
contract on a trading platform.
Discern what you're able to do in
the options market as a contract writer
or owner.
Interpret different stock
options positions and
tell whether a given position is in or
out of the money.
Well, for futures, you should now be
able to describe examples of futures
contracts and their use for
producers and hedgers.
You should be able to outline the basic
mechanics of the futures market, including
futures contracts and the role of the
futures marketplace for price discovery.
You should also be aware that
margin requirements can and
will change from time to time, especially
in the event of market volatility.
You should now have a basic understanding
of the options and futures markets.
Which will help you advance
to more nuanced features and
complex trading strategies
specific to these asset classes.
I'm Steven Levine with
Interactive Brokers.
We thank you for
participating in this derivatives course.
[MUSIC]